Welcome to my new series: Close Enough Lore
Where I, Kilian, tell backstories
That might not be entirely correct but, they are, close enough.
On this episode Skyrim's backstory.
First we need to go back hundreds of years.
This is Tamriel. This is Akavir.
In Akavir a couple of dragons were playing Monopoly.
The leader Alduin said:
"Skyrim seems pretty great."
"Got 94 on Metacritic."
"We should conquer it."
"..or we could take over a place that isn't a frozen shithole!"
"Stop it with the negative attitude, Alan!"
The dragons flew to Skyrim and seized control of it.
And the humans did everything they said because dragons have high speech skill.
They ruled humanity for about 15 minutes
Then every person on all of Tamriel decided to attack the dragons simultaneously
Because one dragon touched a chicken.
Bethesda aren't famous for their intelligent AI.
The dragons were forced to hide in caves because they were too proud to pay the 5 septim fine.
"Could have gone better, where is Paarthurnax?"
"He used the console to change faction!"
"That treacherous asshole!"
"So the problem with our invasion was they all attacked us together."
"So before we attack again let's wait until they start a civil war."
"That could take centuries."
"Actually, it might never happen."
"I know, Alan! I am prepared!"
"Steam had a sale and guess who bought everyone a copy of Brave New World!"
"Only I get to play Poland."
A couple of centuries pass and Tamriel now has these two powerful nations called "The Empire" and these assholes.
The assholes gave the empire an ultinatum.
"Give us all your gold and all your land! Then ban that religion that they have in Skyrim!"
"Seriously, worshiping a human is racist."
"If you don't we'll invade!"
"LET'S DO THIS!"
So they had war and they stopped having war.
"Fine, we'll sign a peace treaty."
"You don't have to give us all your gold, you don't have to give us all your land,"
"But seriously man, like-"
"Honestly, fuck Skyrim."
The empire agrees to ban Talos worship.
Who is Talos? Well, that's actually a very long story.
He was this 20 year old general that said:
"I should unite Tamriel."
Then he did that. The end.
Jarl Ulfric didn't like his religion getting banned so he said:
"I'm so angry at the empire."
"I'm gonna take out my anger,"
"On someone else."
So he kills Skyrim's High King.
Now the Skyrim Civil War has started.
The Empire with their thousands of troops, master mages and latest in sieged technology
Versus the Stormcloaks which consists about 14 farmers.
To be honest it's surprisingly even.
To be fair the Stormcloaks have Skyrim horses.
That are about as powerful as apache helicopters.
Ulfric is captured and sentenced to exile
But he gets unlucky and winds up in the same cart with a public masturbator.
On his way to his execution in Helgen.
And you are the masturbator.
If you're interested in more Skyrim lore,
Why? I pretty much covered everything and that is the Kilian Experience.
Hello there. Check out my parody reviews.
I may- I spe- spend a lot of time on them please do that
Like maybe. No